[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "So it's quite a messy situation, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "That's right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 95, "question": "Could you explain what that means?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "IN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 96, "answer": "Yes, that's right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["AMANDA KNOX"]}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "''", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "Are you concerned about the kind of celebrification of her through this case and the kind of pressure that will now put on her when she tries to return to normal life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "THE TRIALS OF AMANDA KNOX\": Well, I don't know that there's been a lot of celebrification going on as much as demonization.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "How have they all been bearing up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "VBN", "VBG", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "Well, it's been incredibly difficult, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "Do you believe that she was guilty of lying?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "No, I don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "Thomas, I mean, do you believe the family feel so angry about the defamation conviction that they may seek to have that overturned?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "I can't speak for the family.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "What was your overall take of the whole thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "You know, Piers, my overall take was there was nothing that I could glean from this young lady's history that suggested anything like the way she was portrayed in the Italian press or by the -- by the prosecutors in this case.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "But from your assessment what kind of woman is Amanda Knox?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "There's two things I want to comment on that, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Amanda Knox"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["Michael"]}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "What is your primary motivation in going public now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "Well, Piers, Michael is no longer with us, obviously.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "Did you find that with him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "RB", "IN", "NN", "TO", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "Like a good businessman, would you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "Yes, Michael had great instincts, particularly with regard to marketing and promotion.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "He must have thought you were a genius, didn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "Well, Michael was the genius.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "But in terms of the Beatles music, is that still part of Michael's estate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "Absolutely, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1985"]}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "And in terms of the sheer number crunching here, could you tell me now what he paid for it and what it might now be worth?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "Well, we bought the catalog in 1985.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "So he took it from 40-odd million to $1 billion?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "CD", "TO", "$", "CD", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$1 billion"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["John MaClean", "Michael Jackson"]}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", ":", "VB", "POS", "NN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "What kind of decisions have you taken which have turned out to be very smart ones in relation to handling his estate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "TO", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "Well, my co-executor John MaClean and I -- let's face it, Piers, we're fortunate to represent Michael Jackson.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "What would you say to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "I'm not sure if that's true or not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "How did he seem to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "It wasn't a long meeting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "In all your experience of working in the entertainment industry, how did Michael's business empire rank?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "Michael truly was one of a kind.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "But was his spending out of control, as people kept saying it was?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "Well, that was an area that was handled by Michael's business managers and accountants.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "How do their estates compare in terms of how you manage them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "Well, it's hard to compare.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "How fast have those assets appreciated since his death?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "Well, you know, we've tried to do the right things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "Am I right in thinking the estate is already petitioned to distribute 30 million dollars to the will's beneficiaries, who would be his immediate family and children?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "MD", "POS", "NNS", ",", "WP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["30 million dollars"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mrs. Jackson", "Michael"]}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "John, presumably as the co-executor, would you have read the will to the family?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "MD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "Yes, I did, to Mrs. Jackson and several of Michael's siblings.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "How was that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "Very emotional.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "Were you aware that that 2002 will was still in play?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "CD", "MD", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "No, not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2002"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "Are they in a more relaxed frame of mind about it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "RBR", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "I would think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "That's true, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "That's right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2013"], "LOCATION": ["Las Vegas"]}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "VBN", "RB", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "In 2013, it goes to Vegas permanently and there will be a Michael Jackson Museum?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "NNP", "RB", "CC", "EX", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "There will be another show that's created permanently and specifically for a theater in Las Vegas in 2013.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2013"], "PERSON": ["Michael Jackson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Conrad Murray"]}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", ",", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "What do you make of all this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "The issue in this case will be, did Conrad Murray engage in the appropriate standard of care for a physician in that situation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "CC", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "What do you think of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "I think the pressures of any allegations, even though they're false and even though it turns out you're acquitted, put tremendous pressure on you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "What did you think of his status as a performer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "I think it was unparalleled.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Berry Gordy"]}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "WP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "What do you think his legacy will be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "As Berry Gordy said, the greatest performer who ever lived.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Jackson"]}, "docId": "111003pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "Howard?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "For me, when people ask me to describe Michael Jackson, I say push the play button on the video or on your iPod and that says it all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]